Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=The Palace Gambit=
=مناورة القصر=
=Episode 2=
=الحلقة الثانية=
(I Enjoy Handling Lowlifes)
(أنا استمتع بالتعامل مع الأشخاص السيئين)
- Wan'er! - Her Highness said it.
- وانر! - قالت سموها.
Wan'er.
وانر.
Beauty Song,
أغنية الجمال،
remember clearly
تذكر بوضوح
the taste of the whip's punishment.
طعم عقوبة السوط.
- Stop it! - Learn your lessons.
- توقف! - تعلم دروسك.
Wan'er did nothing wrong!
وانر لم يفعل شيئا خاطئا!
Why are you torturing her?
لماذا تعذبها؟
You've framed her!
لقد أحاطت بها التهمة!
Jiuning, shut up!
جيونينج، اصمت!
Release me!
أطلق سراحي!
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Stop beating her!
توقف عن ضربها!
Stop it!
اوقفها!
Wan'er.
وانر.
All you ladies,
جميعكم سيداتي،
look at this.
أنظر إلى هذا.
The one being beaten
الشخص الذي يتعرض للضرب
is Beauty Song.
هي أغنية الجمال.
She is presented to His Majesty from outside the palace.
يتم تقديمها لجلالته من خارج القصر.
When serving His Majesty in the future,
عند خدمة جلالته في المستقبل،
you must strive by any means to win his favor.
يجب عليك أن تسعى بكل الوسائل لكسب رضاه.
In this harem,
في هذا الحريم،
those who lose imperial favor
أولئك الذين يفقدون النعمة الإمبراطورية
become lower than swine and dogs.
يصبحون أدنى من الخنازير والكلاب.
No matter what, she's His Majesty's woman.
مهما كان الأمر، فهي امرأة جلالته.
How dare they humiliate her?
كيف يجرؤون على إهانتها؟
The favored consorts here
الزوجات المفضلات هنا
not only hold higher ranks
لا يحملون رتبًا أعلى فحسب
but also come from noble families.
لكنهم يأتون أيضًا من عائلات نبيلة.
Crushing a mere beauty
سحق مجرد الجمال
is easier than squashing an ant.
أسهل من سحق نملة.
Alright, ladies.
حسنًا سيداتي.
Cease your muttering.
توقف عن تمتماتك.
Let's go now.
دعنا نذهب الآن.
Stop the whipping!
اوقفوا الضرب!
Enough!
كافٍ!
Wan'er.
وانر.
Move.
يتحرك.
Wake up, Wan'er!
استيقظ يا وان'ير!
(Imperial Hospital) Physician! Open the door!
(المستشفى الإمبراطوري) يا طبيب! افتح الباب!
Physician!
طبيب!
Physician, please open up!
يا طبيب، من فضلك افتح!
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
My lady is injured.
سيدتي مصابة.
I need an ointment to ease her pain.
أحتاج إلى مرهم لتخفيف آلامها.
Which palace do you serve?
أي قصر تخدم؟
Lijing Pavilion.
جناح ليجينغ.
Too late. Return tomorrow morning.
لقد فات الأوان. سأعود غدًا صباحًا.
Don't shut the door!
لا تغلق الباب!
Physician!
طبيب!
I've brought gifts for you.
لقد أحضرت لك هدايا.
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
Physician!
طبيب!
Physician, I beg you!
يا طبيب أرجوك!
Please open!
من فضلك افتح!
Halt!
وقف!
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Chunyu.
تشونيو.
This maid appears before me
تظهر هذه الخادمة أمامي
without paying respects.
بدون تقديم الاحترام.
Slap her face.
صفعها على وجهها.
Yes.
نعم.
We never offended you.
نحن لم نسيء إليك أبدًا.
Why did you frame Wan'er?
لماذا قمت بتأطير وان إير؟
How dare you question me!
كيف تجرؤ على سؤالي؟
It's okay to tell you why.
ليس من العيب أن أخبرك لماذا.
Lowborn hussies with pretty faces
عاهرات متواضعات ذوات وجوه جميلة
dare compete with noble-born ladies like us?
هل تجرؤ على التنافس مع السيدات النبيلات مثلنا؟
You're unworthy!
أنت لا تستحق!
Learn a lesson from what happened today.
تعلم درسًا مما حدث اليوم.
Behave meekly henceforth.
تصرف بوداعة من الآن فصاعدا.
Though lowborn,
على الرغم من كونه من أصل متواضع،
we seek no trouble.
نحن لا نسعى إلى المتاعب.
Lowborn hussies
العاهرات المتواضعات
shouldn't be beautiful.
لا ينبغي أن تكون جميلة.
You know what?
أتعلم؟
I enjoy handling lowlifes.
أستمتع بالتعامل مع الأشخاص المنحطين.
Countless beauties enter the harem yearly,
يدخل عدد لا يحصى من الجميلات إلى الحريم سنويًا،
but none survive three months.
ولكن لا أحد منهم يبقى على قيد الحياة لمدة ثلاثة أشهر.
Within three months,
خلال ثلاثة أشهر،
I'll destroy you.
سأدمرك.
You wish!
انت تتمنى!
If you drive us up the wall,
إذا دفعتنا إلى الحائط،
I will
أنا سوف
do anything to fight back.
افعل أي شيء للرد.
Very tough.
صعبة للغاية.
Let me see
دعني أرى
what you can do
ما يمكنك فعله
to challenge me.
لتحديني.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
You don't know what we've endured
أنت لا تعرف ما تحملناه
and how many bad men we've met.
وكم من الرجال السيئين التقينا بهم.
Some used human blood for cure
استخدم البعض الدم البشري للعلاج
and made incense holders from human bones.
وصنعوا حاملات البخور من عظام الإنسان.
Some forced servants
بعض الخدم القسريين
to use hands with torn-off fingernails
استخدام اليدين بأظافر ممزقة
to massage their legs.
لتدليك أرجلهم.
You can't imagine
لا يمكنك التخيل
what we've endured.
ما تحملناه.
But no matter what,
ولكن مهما كان الأمر،
we just want to survive.
نريد فقط البقاء على قيد الحياة.
We don't seek trouble.
نحن لا نبحث عن المتاعب.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
don't provoke us again.
لا تستفزنا مرة أخرى
We'll coexist peacefully.
سوف نتعايش بسلام.
But if
ولكن إذا
you deny us a chance to live,
أنت تحرمنا من فرصة العيش،
I swear to you
أقسم لك
I'll make you regret
سأجعلك تندم
ever meeting me.
هل تقابلني من قبل؟
(Lijing Pavilion)
(جناح ليجينغ)
This is all my fault.
كل هذا خطئي.
I got you beaten too.
لقد ضربتك أيضا.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
It doesn't hurt.
إنه لا يؤلم.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
on my way back,
في طريق عودتي،
I met Lady Yu.
التقيت بالسيدة يو.
She admitted framing you
لقد اعترفت بتوريطك
out of jealousy for your beauty.
من الغيرة على جمالك.
Why are the women in this harem
لماذا النساء في هذا الحريم
so vicious?
شرسة جداً؟
Jiuning.
جيونينج.
Perhaps I was naive.
ربما كنت ساذجا.
I thought
اعتقدت
keeping quiet
التزام الصمت
and staying low
والبقاء منخفضا
would let us survive.
سوف يسمح لنا بالبقاء على قيد الحياة.
But this incident made me realize
لكن هذا الحادث جعلني أدرك
that in the harem,
أن في الحريم،
those without power
أولئك الذين ليس لديهم قوة
who don't dare to fight
الذين لا يجرؤون على القتال
are destined to perish.
مقدر لهم الهلاك.
Are you saying
هل انت تقول
you'll compete for favor?
هل ستتنافسون على الحظوة؟
Better to take risks
من الأفضل المخاطرة
than endure their abuse.
من أن تتحمل إساءتهم.
Aren't they just afraid
أليسوا خائفين فقط؟
I'll outshine them?
هل سأتفوق عليهم؟
Since they fear it,
لأنهم يخافون منه،
I'll fight harder
سأقاتل بقوة أكبر
to seize every opportunity.
لاغتنام كل فرصة.
But we are powerless.
ولكننا عاجزون.
The path ahead
الطريق إلى الأمام
will be perilous.
سيكون خطيرا.
Fighting might kill us.
القتال قد يقتلنا.
But not fighting
ولكن ليس القتال
means certain death.
يعني موتًا مؤكدًا.
Even the slimmest hope
حتى أضعف الأمل
is worth pursuing.
يستحق المتابعة.
I won't stay trampled underfoot
لن أبقى مدوسًا تحت الأقدام
like an ant.
مثل النملة.
Countless beauties enter the harem yearly,
يدخل عدد لا يحصى من الجميلات إلى الحريم سنويًا،
but none survive three months.
ولكن لا أحد منهم يبقى على قيد الحياة لمدة ثلاثة أشهر.
Within three months,
خلال ثلاثة أشهر،
I'll destroy you all.
سأدمركم جميعا.
A desperate struggle
صراع يائس
might bring new hope.
ربما يجلب أملا جديدا.
You possess unmatched beauty.
أنت تمتلك جمالا لا مثيل له.
You are versatile in arts.
أنت متعدد المواهب في الفنون.
If you compete
إذا كنت تنافس
for His Majesty's favor,
لصالح جلالته،
you can surpass them.
يمكنك التفوق عليهم.
If you're resolved,
إذا كنت قد قررت،
I'll stand with you.
سأقف معك.
Even at the cost of my life,
حتى لو كان ذلك على حساب حياتي،
I'll protect you.
سأحميك.
Wan'er.
وانر.
Jiuning.
جيونينج.
Don't sacrifice yourself.
لا تضحي بنفسك.
You're my only family left.
أنت عائلتي الوحيدة المتبقية.
We must strive together
يجب علينا أن نسعى معًا
to survive.
من أجل البقاء.
Yes.
نعم.
Even through stormy paths,
حتى من خلال المسارات العاصفة،
we must
يجب علينا
carve our way out.
شق طريقنا للخروج.
(Lady Yu,)
(السيدة يو)
(if you hurt Wan'er again,)
(إذا أذيت وان إير مرة أخرى)
(I'll make you pay for it.)
(سأجعلك تدفع ثمنها.)
Jiuning.
جيونينج.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm applying the scented ointment
أنا أضع المرهم المعطر
made from nectar and herbs to these plants.
مصنوعة من الرحيق والأعشاب لهذه النباتات.
Why?
لماذا؟
I heard His Majesty
سمعت جلالته
will pass through the corridor tonight.
سوف تمر عبر الممر الليلة.
I'm trying
انا احاول
to bring His Majesty over to meet you.
لإحضار جلالته لمقابلتك.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
How can His Majesty do what you say?
كيف يستطيع جلالته أن يفعل ما تقوله؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
If His Majesty passes by, it'll surely work.
إذا مر جلالته، فإن الأمر سينجح بالتأكيد.
You must shine tonight.
يجب عليك أن تتألق الليلة.
This is your big day.
هذا هو يومك الكبير.
We'll wait and see.
سوف ننتظر ونرى.
(Imperial Study)
(دراسة إمبراطورية)
(Emperor)
(الإمبراطور)
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
It's getting late.
لقد أصبح الوقت متأخرًا.
Time to choose.
حان وقت الاختيار.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
A few days ago,
منذ بضعة أيام،
(Eunuch Zhang, Imperial Attendant) When Consort Chun played chess with you,
(الخصي تشانغ، الخادم الإمبراطوري) عندما لعبت معك السيدة تشون الشطرنج،
she defeated you.
لقد هزمتك.
Pleased by this,
مسرور بهذا،
you promised Consort Chun
لقد وعدت قرينتي تشون
to dine with her at her palace
لتناول العشاء معها في قصرها
on the tenth of this month.
في العاشر من هذا الشهر.
Today is the tenth.
اليوم هو العاشر.
Now that you mention it,
الآن بعد أن ذكرت ذلك،
I do recall.
انا أتذكر.
It's been too long since I drank with her.
لقد مر وقت طويل منذ أن شربت معها.
(Consort Chun)
(القرينة تشون)
To Chengxi Palace!
إلى قصر تشنغشي!
Yes.
نعم.
(Chengxi Palace)
(قصر تشنغشي)
- Your Highness.
- صاحب السمو.
Tonight marks Her Highness's huge occasion.
تصادف الليلة المناسبة الكبرى لصاحبة السمو .
Do your work carefully.
قم بعملك بعناية.
Don't make any mistake.
لا ترتكب أي خطأ.
If you jeopardize the plan,
إذا عرضت الخطة للخطر،
(Jinping, Chief Maid) you'll lose your heads.
(جين بينغ، رئيسة الخادمات) سوف تفقدون رؤوسكم.
- Yes.
- نعم.
Congrats!
تهاني!
Finally, the day has come.
وأخيرا جاء اليوم.
The once-in-a-century Seven-Star Conjunction
اقتران النجوم السبعة الذي يحدث مرة واحدة في القرن
will show up.
سوف تظهر.
The Imperial Astrologer divined
وقد تنبأ المنجم الإمبراطوري
that if Your Highness serves tonight,
أنه إذا خدم سموكم الليلة،
you'll surely conceive an heir.
من المؤكد أنك ستحصل على وريث.
In the future,
في المستقبل،
through your son's prestige,
من خلال مكانة ابنك،
you'll ascend to become Empress.
سوف ترتقي لتصبح الإمبراطورة.
I've served His Majesty for years,
لقد خدمت جلالته لسنوات،
yet never conceived.
ولكن لم يتم تصوره أبدًا.
If I succeed this time,
إذا نجحت هذه المرة،
I'll never bow to the woman in Yongxiu Palace.
لن أنحني أبدًا أمام المرأة في قصر يونغشيو.
Pardon me, please.
عفوا من فضلك.
Spare me, please.
أرجوك أنقذني.
Mercy, Your Highness!
رحمتك يا صاحب السمو!
You vile fool!
أيها الأحمق الحقير!
You're so useless.
أنت عديم الفائدة تماما.
Guards!
حراس!
Drag her out and execute her!
إسحبها وأعدمها!
Wait.
انتظر.
Jinping.
جين بينغ.
Tonight is important to me.
الليلة مهمة بالنسبة لي.
No bloodshed tonight.
لا سفك للدماء الليلة.
Don't jinx my fortune.
لا تجلب الحظ السيئ لي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank you for your mercy.
شكرا لرحمتك.
Take her away
خذها بعيدا
and bury her alive somewhere.
ودفنها حية في مكان ما.
Your Highness!
صاحب السمو!
Spare me!
انقذني!
Spare me, Your Highness!
ارحمني يا صاحب السمو!
Your Highness!
صاحب السمو!
Congrats, Your Highness!
مبروك يا صاحب السمو!
His Majesty
صاحب الجلالة
has departed for Chengxi Palace!
لقد غادر إلى قصر تشنغشي!
His Majesty finally comes!
جلالته يأتي أخيرا!
Jinping.
جين بينغ.
Xiao Dezi.
شياو ديزي.
Serve flawlessly tonight!
قدمها بلا عيوب الليلة!
This heaven-sent opportunity comes once a century.
إن هذه الفرصة السماوية تأتي مرة واحدة كل قرن.
If anyone ruins my plans,
إذا قام أي شخص بتخريب خططي،
you'll never see the dawn again.
لن ترى الفجر مرة أخرى
- Yes.
- نعم.
So many!
كثير جدا!
More over there!
المزيد هناك!
Let me see!
دعني أرى!
Look!
ينظر!
Where are they from?
من أين هم؟
Look.
ينظر.
How beautiful!
كم هو جميل!
These fireflies are transformed
لقد تحولت هذه اليراعات
from the rainbow under the fairies' feet.
من قوس قزح تحت أقدام الجنيات.
On nights with fireflies,
في الليالي مع اليراعات،
the fairy maidens will come.
سوف تأتي الفتيات الجنيات.
Here!
هنا!
Who's there?
من هناك؟
What did you just say?
ماذا قلت للتو؟
Answer His Majesty!
أجب جلالته!
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
I just spoke of a tale.
لقد تحدثت للتو عن قصة.
My mother told me about it
لقد أخبرتني أمي بذلك
when I was little.
عندما كنت صغيرا.
It is
إنها
about fireflies that are transformed
عن اليراعات التي تتحول
from the rainbow under the fairy maidens' feet.
من قوس قزح تحت أقدام العذارى الجنيات.
On nights with fireflies,
في الليالي مع اليراعات،
perhaps an immortal fairy who develops mortal desires
ربما جنية خالدة تنمي رغبات بشرية
will come down
سوف ينزل
to meet her beloved.
للقاء حبيبها.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Get ready to...
استعد ل...
Lower it.
اخفضه.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
The Garden's that way.
الحديقة في هذا الاتجاه.
Chengxi Palace is this way.
قصر تشنغشي موجود بهذا الطريق.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Come on!
تعال!
Follow up!
متابعة!
- Yes.
- نعم.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.